A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nurses - Staff - Williston, Agnes, 1919-1921 (Box 107, Folder 766A)
- Nurses - Staff (Wol-Won) (Box 107, Folder 767)
  Wolf, Anna D., 1918-1927, 1930-1934, 1949, 1970; Wong, Cora J., 1919-1926; Wong, (Chien-chen) Margaret, 1931-1932, 1944
  Items of special note in this folder include Ring Insignia for Nursing School, attached to a letter from Wolf to Eggleston (April 29, 1924), found under the mark-up Nurses - Staff - Wolf.
- Nurses - Staff (Woo-Wy) (Box 107, Folder 768)
  Wooster, Maude, 1922-1923; Wu, Chin-yu, 1944; Wu, Liang-fu, 1924; Wyne, Margaret R., 1921, 1928-1934, 1938-1949, 1953, 1957
- Nurses - Staff (Y-Z) (Box 107, Folder 769)
  Yang, Jui-chun, 1935; Yang, Kuei-chen, 1948-1950; Yang, (Yu-feng) Laura, 1941, 1946; Yang, Pei-chen, 1949; Yang, Ying-chen, 1949; Yang, Ying-hua, 1949-1950; Yang, Yi-wen, 1948-1950; Yih, Wei-li, 1925; Ying, (Hsi-ying) Elizabeth, 1955; Young, Lucy B., 1931-1934; Yu, Fang-lien, 1947; Yu, Fu-ching, 1933-1937; Yuan, Yi-chu, 1941; Zia, Ruth V. M., 1938-1940, 1952-1955
- Nurses - Supervisor Memoranda (A-Z), 1927-1928 (Box 107, Folder 770)
  Addison, Madge; Auld, Harriet; Bohart, Marjory; Brooke, Elizabeth; Cameron, Gladys; Carter, Lucy B.; Crandall, Lu; Drake, Mary; Dunbar, Virginia; Furnival, Christine; Grey, Grace; Harrison, Julie; Hollen, Agnes; Holtz, Elsie; Horner, Elva; Kepler, aura; Linka, Lydia; MacKennon, Marion; Madden, Margaret; Marshall, Dorris; McDermott, Anne; McFarland, Katherine; Melvoid, Charlotte; Miller, Hilde; Moran, Elizabeth; Newman, Edna; Nichols, Blanche; Noyes, Harriet; O'Brian, Margaret; Odgen, Mary; Pease, Hellen; Pierson, Ethel; Rogers, Mary; Savage, Eleanor; Savage, R. E.; Smith, Harriet; Smith, Martha; Smith, Sallie; Tilghman, Gabriela; Thornburgh, Marion; Valentine, Josephne; Wagner, Belle; Wangen, Clare; Watt, Jean M.; Young, Adeline
- Nu-Ny (Box 107, Folder 771)
  Nurses Association of China, 1925-1928, 1933, 1944-1946 (Goodrich, L. C.; Ingram; Kweiyang Nursing School; Nursing Journal of China, 1936-1941; Parson, Maude; Simpson, Cora E.; Yuan, I. C.) Nursing School of Chengtu, 1943 Nyi, P. C., 1947 Nyi, Tsung-tsong, 1925-1933
- Obstetric Manual, 1940 (Box 107, Folder 772)
- Oc-Ol (Box 107, Folder 773)
  Occupational Therapy, 1932-1935, 1959-1960 (Bullington, Tirzah E.; Greene; Kimm, H. T.) Office Routine, 1928-1931, 1949-1950 (Filing; Greene; Rental; Vincent) O'Leary, James J., 1930 Oliver, W. W., 1929
- Opthalmology, 1916, 1920-1926 (Box 108, Folder 774)
- Opthalmology, 1926-1940 (Box 108, Folder 775)
  Cash; Director; Downing, Augustus S.; Dunlap; Embree, Edwin; Greene; Gregg; Houghton; Howard, Harvey J.; Li, T. M.; Macmillan, E.B.A.; Pearce, Richard M.
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Bock - Chang, S.P.) (Box 108, Folder 776)
  Bock, Rudolf H., 1945-1959, 1966; Burch, Frank E., 1939-1940, 1946-1948; Chang, E., 1938; Chang, Hsiao-lou, 1940-1941, 1950; Chang, Shih-pu, 1929-1939
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Chang, T.F. - Feng) (Box 108, Folder 777)
  Chang, Tsu-feng, 1924-1927; Chao, Chen-nei, 1937-1938; Chen, Hsi-li, 1936-1937; Chen, Hsi-teh, 1929; Chen, Wen-yuin, 1934-1935; Chi, Hsu-che, 1934-1935; Ching, Renald P., 1933-1936, 1950; Chou, Chen-hu, 1927; Chu, Cheng-fang, 1927; Chung, Elbert Y., 1924-1928; Daniel, Ruby K., 1935-1939; Den, Kwee-chuan, 1935; Dzen, Ts-tswang, 1921-1923; Fan, Chang-sung, 1934-1936, 1950-1953; Feng, Hui-hsi (Marie), 1931-1933, 1938-1939, 1949, 1954, 1969
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Fu-Hon) (Box 108, Folder 778)
  Fuchs, Adalbert, 1922-1927, 1933, 1946, 1949, 1954, 1969-1971; Fuchs, Ernst, 1922-1923, 1930; Hall, James H., 1922-1923; Hong, 1922
- Ophthalmology - Staff - Howard, H. J., 1914-July 1925 (Box 108, Folder 779)
- Ophthalmology - Staff - Howard, H. J., August 1925-1956 (Box 108, Folder 780)
  Items of special note in this folder include a report, with photographs, by A. P. Chien on relief of Dr. Howard, captured by bandits (1925).
- Ophthalmology - Staff (How-Kr) (Box 109, Folder 781)
  Howard, Paul R., 1922; James, 1922; John, Isa, 1930-1932; Kiang, Sing-mei, 1930; Kronfield, Peter C., 1933-1942, 1946, 1951, 1964
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Kung - Li, M.) (Box 109, Folder 782)
  Kung, Hsien-gieh, 1934; Lai, Tsung-yao, 1922-1926; Lam, Tin-kwan, 1930; Lan, Yee-shun, 1926; Lao, Katherine Y. S., 1950; Lee, Tau-piew, 1922-1930; Li, (Yoeh-mei) Marion, 1940
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Li, T.M. - Liang, P.P.) (Box 109, Folder 783)
  Li, Tsing-meu, 1917-1928, 1932; Li, T. P., 1932; Liang, Pao-ping, 1925-1927, 1951-1957
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Pao-ping Liang and family (October 28, 1951) and a photograph of Pao-ping Liang (May 29, 1953).
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Liang, S.C. - Luo) (Box 109, Folder 784)
  Liang, Shao-chao, 1938; Lin, Ching-kuei, 1932-1940, 1945; Ling, Chih-huan, 1926; Ling, Wen-ping, 1919-1926, 1930-1933; Liu, Gia-chi, 1937-1938; Liu, Pau-hua, 1928-1929; Luo, Tsung-hsien, 1932-1950
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Mi-Pi) (Box 109, Folder 785)
  Miller, Ira M., 1922; Pan, Tso-hsin, 1928; Pi, Hua-teh, 1921-1927, 1932-1939, 1946
- Ophthalmology - Staff - Pillat, Arnold, 1926-1940, 1947, 1950, 1963-1964 (Box 109, Folder 786)
- Ophthalmology - Staff (Sa-So) (Box 109, Folder 787)
  Sallmann, Ludwig, 1929-1931; Schweinitz, G. E. de, 1922, 1927; Soudakoff, Peter, 1925-1926, 1932-1947, 1952, 1960
- Ophthalmology - Staff (St-Ya) (Box 109, Folder 788)
  Stuckey, Edward, J., 1916-1918; Sui, Jen-tseng, 1938-1939; Sun, Kuei-shu, 1948; Sun, Shui-cheng, 1939-1940; Sung, Chih-jen, 1941; Tai, Meng-chun, 1928; Tang, Paul R., 1921-1922; Teng, Chih-chiang, 1935-1936; Woods, Alan C., 1917; Yang, (Hsien-chin) Robert, 1937
- Organ, 1925-1928 (Box 110, Folder 789)
  Comptroller; Director; Dunlap
- Organization, 1914 (Box 110, Folder 790)
- Organization, 1915 (Box 110, Folder 791)
- Organization, 1916-1925 (Box 110, Folder 792)
- Organization, 1926 (Box 110, Folder 793)
- Organization, 1927 (Box 110, Folder 794)
- Organization, 1927 June-November (Box 110, Folder 795)
- Organization, 1928 November-December (Box 110, Folder 796)
- Organization, 1929 January-February (Box 111, Folder 797)
- Organization, 1929 March (Box 111, Folder 798)
- Organization, 1929 April-December (Box 111, Folder 799)
- Organization, 1930-1932 (Box 111, Folder 800)
- Organization, 1933 (Box 111, Folder 801)
- Organization, 1934-1935 (Box 111, Folder 802)
- Organization, 1936 January-February (Box 111, Folder 803)
- Organization, 1936 March-December (Box 112, Folder 804)
- Organization, 1937 January-June (Box 112, Folder 805)
- Organization, 1937 July-December (Box 112, Folder 806)
- Organization, 1938-1939 (Box 112, Folder 807)
- Organization, 1940-1941 (Box 112, Folder 808)
- Organization, 1942-1950 (Box 112, Folder 809)
  Administration; Advisory Committee (Brown, Arthur J.; Debevoise; Greene; Houghton; Monroe, Paul; Rockefeller, J. D. Jr.; Rockefeller, J. D. 3rd; Weir, H. H.; Welch, William H.); Amoss; Appleget; Ballou, Earle H.; Barton, James L.; Bassett, Arthur; Berglund; Brind, Charles A.; Brown, Arthur J.; Chinese Advisory Committee - Buttrick, Wallace; Cochrane, Thomas; Cohn, Alfred E.; Comptroller; Debevoise; Dieuaide; Director; Dunlap; Fang, Shisan C.; Flexner, S.; Fosdick; Gee, N. Gist; Goodrich, L. C.; Grant, J. B.; Greene; Gregg; Gunn, Selskar; Hawkins, F. H.; Houghton; Hu, Shih; Hume, Edward H.; Legal Council - Belknap; Legal Council - Greene; Legal Council - Lin, H. K. (see Trustees - Lin, H. K.); Lim, C. E.; Lim, Robert K. S.; Lobenstine; Loucks; Mason, Max; Maxwell, J. Preston; McLean, Franklin; Memo; Monroe, Paul; Mott, John R.; Name (Bulkley, Charles S.; Debevoise; Greene; Pearce, R. M.; Sullivan, James); Palmer, Walter; Pearce, Richard M.; Peffer, Nat; Rockefeller, John D. Jr.; Rockefeller, John D. 3rd; Secretariat; Sullivan, James; Thompson, Norma S.; Tsur, Y. T.; Vincent; Wu, Lien-teh; Yen, F. C.
- Os-Ot (Box 112, Folder 810)
  Osteomalacia, 1947 (Director); Otology, 1919-1931
- Otology - Staff (Ch-Dr) (Box 112, Folder 811)
  Chang, Ching-sung, 1933, 1937-1940; Cook, Alice, 1920-1923; Drury, Dana W., 1920
- Otology - Staff - Dunlap, Albert M., 1916-1929 (Box 112, Folder 812)
  Items of special note in this folder include photographs of physiological drawings for class.
- Otology - Staff - Dunlap, Albert M., 1930-1966 (Box 113, Folder 813)
- Otology - Staff (H-K) (Box 113, Folder 814)
  Hsu, Yin-hsiang, 1940-1941, 1946, 1950; Hu, Mao-lien, 1924-1934; Kao, Shih-en, 1922-1930; King, Tze, 1921-1926, 1930-1936, 1945; Kung, Hsien-gieh, 1930
- Otology - Staff (La-St) (Box 113, Folder 815)
  Lang, Kuo-chen (Samuel), 1927; Li, Kang, 1921-1922, 1927; Li, Yuan-fu, 1930; Lin, Shih-hsi, 1925-1927; Liu, Jui-hua, 1917-1931, 1936, 1941, 1945-1950; Moo, Jen-fong, 1929; Slack, Harry R., 1922-1923; Stone, Henry A., 1924-1925
- Otology - Staff (Su-Ts) (Box 113, Folder 816)
  Sung, Chung-yi, 1924; Ting, Yung-hao, 1924-1936; Tsen, Shih-ping, 1925-1926
- Pac-Pao (Box 113, Folder 817)
  Pacific Coast Medical Bureau, 1947; Pai, Shih-en, 1926-1928, 1944-1949; Pan Pacific Conference, 1925 (Greene; Gregory, Herbert E.; Houghton); Paotingfu Provincial Medical School, 1947
- Parasitology, 1919-1928, 1932, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 818)
  Amoss; Cash, James R.; Director; Faust; Greene; Hoeppli; Houghton; Mills, Ralph G.; Pearce; Welch
- Parasitology - Staff (C) (Box 113, Folder 819)
  Chu, Hai-ju, 1948-1950 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Cort, William W., 1922-1924, 1939, 1945-1946, 1961-1962, 1971
- Parasitology - Staff - Faust, Ernest C., 1919-1961 (Box 113, Folder 820)
- Parasitology - Staff - Feng, Lan-chou, 1938, 1945-1950 (Box 113, Folder 821)
  See also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal
- Parasitology - Staff - Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1927-1941 (Box 114, Folder 822)
- Parasitology - Staff - Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1942-1948 (Box 114, Folder 823)
- Parasitology - Staff - Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1949-1970 (Box 114, Folder 824)
- Parasitology - Staff - Hsu, Hsi-fan, 1935, 1940-1949, 1953-1954 (Box 114, Folder 825)
- Parasitology - Staff (K-S) (Box 114, Folder 826)
  Khow, Oo-kek, 1927-1928, 1931-1945; Li, Hsi-chieh, 1931; Stoll, Norman R., 1923-1924; Svenson, Ruth M., 1924-1925, 1950
- Par-Pat (Box 114, Folder 827)
  Parasuhin, S., 1936 Parge, Lola, 1950-1953 Paris Office, 1931-1934 (Gunn; Tennant, Elizabeth) Parker, George H., 1926 Patents, 1931-1932, 1942: Anti-Opium Treatment (Edsall; Greene; Gregg; Kendall; Mason; Reid, M.; Vincent); Mills Laboratories (Beardsley, W. R.; Debevoise)
- Pathology, 1921-1927 (Box 114, Folder 828)
- Pathology, 1928-1937 (Box 114, Folder 829)
  Amoss; Cash, James R.; Director; Dunlap; Flexner, S.; Greene; Houghton; Hu; Karsnser, Howard; MacCallum, William G.; McLean, Franklin C.; Pearce; Rich, Arnold; Smetana; Ten Broeck
- Pathology - Staff - Bartlett, Clifford L., 1922-1930, 1937, 1942-1943, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 830)
- Pathology - Staff (Cash-Chan) (Box 115, Folder 831)
  Cash, James R., 1924-1932, 1947-1949, 1958-1960, 1971; Chang, Chia-ching, 1948; Chang, Tai-ho, 1948
- Pathology - Staff (Chao-Co) (Box 115, Folder 832)
  Chao, Hsiu-ling, 1948; Chen, Wen-kwei, 1929-1931; Chin, Kuang-yu, 1936-1941, 1945-1946 (see also Publications - China Medical Journal); Councilman, William T., 1922-1925, 1933
- Pathology - Staff (Fe-Hs) (Box 115, Folder 833)
  Feng, Lan-chou, 1929-1937, 1947 (see also Parasitology); Field, Florence, 1922; Garber, C. Zeng, 1928-1935; Hektoen, Ludwig, 1928; Ho, Euchen, 1927; Hou, B. D., 1922; Hsieh, En-tseng, 1918-1921; Hsu, K. L., 1927; Hsu, Ying-tang, 1926, 1945-1947, 1954, 1968-1971
- Pathology - Staff - Hu, Cheng-hsiang, 1924-1947 (Box 115, Folder 834)
- Pathology - Staff (Hu-Kia) (Box 115, Folder 835)
  Hu, Ying-tang, 1948-1971; Kang, Hsi-jung, 1926-1936, 1945, 1951-1954; Kessel, John F., 1923-1929, 1933; Kiang, (Pen-kuang) David V., 1926-1928
- Pathology - Staff (Kim-Li) (Box 115, Folder 836)
  Kimm, Hsien-chai, 1930; Kindell, F. B., 1927; Koo, Chee-hwa, 1940; Ku, Djeng-yan, 1929; Ku, Yun-yu, 1932-1933; Kwan, Han-ping, 1938-1940; Li, Chen-pien, 1926-1933; Li, P. L., 1932; Li, Tei-lin, 1931; Li, Ting-an, 1925-1928
- Pathology - Staff (Lim - Liu, T.C.) (Box 116, Folder 837)
  Lim, Chung-eang, 1925-1930 (see also Bacteriology); Lim, Swee-ngor, 1926; Liu, Teh-chi, 1928
- Pathology - Staff (Liu, Y. - Meleney) (Box 116, Folder 838)
  Liu, Yong, 1947-1950; Ma, Yen-yu, 1928; MacCallum, W. G., 1922-1923; Meleney, Henry E., 1916-1922 (see also Medicine)
- Pathology - Staff - Mills, Ralph G., 1916-1921 (Box 116, Folder 839)
- Pathology - Staff - Mills, Ralph G., 1922-1965 (Box 116, Folder 840)
- Pathology - Staff (Na-Th) (Box 116, Folder 841)
  Nauck, Ernst, 1927; Ngai, Shih-kuang, 1930, 1965; Smetana, Hans, 1925-1933; Tang, Fei-fang, 1925-1928, 1942-1949; Tang, Tien, 1948; Teoh, Beh-lye, 1928; Thompson, William P., 1922-1923
- Pathology - Staff (Ts-Wi) (Box 116, Folder 842)
  Tsen, (Tsung-hsien) Edgar, 1914-1922; Tso, Chi, 1928; Wang, Lo, 1929; Wang, Sui-hsien, 1948; Wang, Tai-ling, 1948; Wang, Teh-hsiu, 1948; Wang, Yung-kwang, 1922-1926; Winternitz, Milton C., undated
- Pathology - Staff (Wu-Yu) (Box 116, Folder 843)
  Wu, Shih-doh, 1941-1948, 1953-1956, 1966 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Yao, Ke-fang, 1926-1927; Yu, Ho, 1926-1929
- Peace Commission, 1945-1947 (Box 117, Folder 844)
  Burwell, C. Sidney; Comptroller; Director; Parker; Stuart, J. Leighton; Ying, Y. C.
  Items of special note in this folder include photographs of Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) as Executive Headquarters (1947); a photograph of Yeh-chien Ying, attached to a letter from Ying to Parker (February 13, 1947); and a telephone directory (November).
- Pearce, A. M. - Pearce, R. M. (Box 117, Folder 845)
  Pearce, Agnes M., 1937, 1941; Pearce, Richard M., 1920-1923, 1928, 1930-1931
  Items of special note in this folder include notes on the Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) (1937, 1941).
- Pediatrics, 1920-1939 (Box 117, Folder 846)
  Blackfan, Kenneth D.; Dieuaide; Director; Greene; Hammond, John; Holt, L. Emmett; Houghton; Howland, John; Pearce, Richard M.; Weech
- Pediatrics - Staff - Black, Arthur P., 1931-1937, 1945, 1950, 1962-1963 (Box 117, Folder 847)
- Pediatrics - Staff (C) (Box 117, Folder 848)
  Chen, (Tsui-chen) Katherine, 1923-1929; Cheng, Jung-pi, 1931; Chu, Fu-tang, 1926-1927, 1930-1941, 1945-1950, 1960, 1964; Chu, Shou-lo, 1949; Chung, Shih-fan, 1930-1933
- Pediatrics - Staff (De-Ha) (Box 117, Folder 849)
  Dietrick, Sarah S., 1929-1935, 1963; Fan, Chuan, 1933-1939, 1945-1947; Hammond, John W., 1922-1931, 1962 (see also Training School)
- Pediatrics - Staff (Ho-Hs) (Box 117, Folder 850)
  Holt, L. Emmett, 1922-1924; Holt, L. Emmett, Jr., 1924, 1927; Hsu, (Ching-feng) Frank, 1941, 1949, 1969-1970; Hsu, Kang-liang, 1924-1928, 1954, 1957
- Pediatrics - Staff (Hs-Ts) (Box 118, Folder 851)
  Hsu, Shih-hsun, 1933, 1952, 1955; Huang, Nan (Nancy), 1941, 1950, 1954; Koo, Chee-hwa, 1941; Lee, Ching-tien, 1950; Lee, Rebeca, 1931-1935; McKhann, Charles F., 1945; McQuarrie, Irvine, 1939, 1955-1956; Niu, Pao-cheng, 1948; Pau, Nien-jo, 1949-1950; Shen, (Chen) Katherine, 1932; Sweet, Lewis K., 1932-1935; Tan, Kuan-lung, 1934; Tsao, Clifford, 1936; Tso, Ernest, 1922-1932, 1941
- Pediatrics - Staff (W) (Box 118, Folder 852)
  Weech, A. Ashley, 1928-1931, 1945-1950; Woo, (Ting) Theresa, 1931-1935, 1941-1945, 1954; Wu, Jui-ping, 1933-1940, 1945
- Pei-Pek (Box 118, Folder 853)
  Pei-ta Medical College, 1946-1947 (Balfour, M. C.; Crocker, Allen C.; Hu, C. H.; Ma, Wen-chao); Peiping Health Department, 1934 (Greene); Peiping Municipal Hospitals, 1933-1935 (Belknap; Debevoise; Greene; Houghton; Vincent); Peking Eye Hospital Fund, 1932-1933 (Greene); Peking International Women's Club (see Housing of Staff Peking Utility Book); Peking Living Conditions, 1919, 1928-1935 (Gamble, Sidney; Greene; Houghton); Peking Man (see Anatomy; Anatomy - Staff; Field Studies - Anthropology; and plaster cast); Peking National University, 1916, 1932-1937, 1945-1947 (Chiang, Mon-lin; Hou, Chung-lien; Wang, Ging-hsi); Peking Office, 1927-1928 (Greene)
  Items of special note in this folder include a monthly index on the cost of living in Peiping, Vol. V, No. 7 (July 1933), found under the mark-up Peking Living Conditions.
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - History and Historical Documents, 1911-1952 (Box 118, Folder 854)
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - History - Reopening (A-Z) (Box 118, Folder 855)
  General, 1943-1947; Balfour, 1945-1946; Ballou, 1944-1945; Bennett, 1945; Bowen, 1945-1946; Chen, C. C., 1944-1946; Chu, C. H., 1945; Cohn, 1945; Dieuaide, 1945; Director, 1945-1947; Dunlap, 1945; Forkner, 1943-1945; Fosdick, 1945-1946; Grant, 1942; Greene, 1945; Gregg, 1944-1945; Hall, 1944; Hinsey, 1945; Houghton, 1945; Hu, 1947; Huang, K. K., 1943; Keefer, 1945-1946; Kilborn, 1945; Library - Hoeppli, 1946; Lim, 1945-1946; Liu, 1945; Loo, 1945; Loucks, 1945-1947; Parker, 1945; Robinson, 1945; Stuart, 1947; Sze, 1945; Tsur, 1945-1946; Wong, 1943; Wu, 1945; Yee, 1945
  Items of special note in this folder include a Chinese character stamp.
- Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - History - Reopening - Replies to Claude E. Forkner Circular, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 856)
  Chang, H. C.; Chang, S. K. P.; Chen, C. C..; Chen, H. I.; Cheng, L.; Chou, C. H.; Chu, C. K.; Huang, K. H.; King; Ku, Y. Y.; Lee; Li, T. A.; Liu, Eva; Liu, W. T.; Pai; Pan; Sia; Soong, T. V.; Tai, T. Y.; Ting, T. P.; Wang, C. W.; Wang, H. Y.; Wang, K. H.; Wang, L. L.; Wu, Y. K.; Yen, C. C.; Yu, H. W.
- Pen-Per (Box 118, Folder 857)
  Penfield, Wilder, 1962-1964 (see also McGill University); Pang, Ta-mou, 1927, 1945; Pennoyer, Willard H., 1945-1946; Pension Fund, 1935-1936 (Comptroller; Greene; Houghton); Perkins, Sara E., 1925, 1944, 1971
  Items of special note in this folder include articles on Peking Union Medical College in the People's Republic of China, found under the mark-up Penfield.
- Personnel, 1919-1941, 1949 (Box 119, Folder 858)
  Director; Frazier; Greene; Houghton; Lim; Loan Fund; Pearce; Resident Director; Rockefeller, John D. 3rd; Snapper; Vincent
- Personnel - Foreign, 1930-1934, 1941 (Box 119, Folder 859)
- Personnel - Openings, 1919-1929, 1936-1939 (Box 119, Folder 860)
  Black, Davidson; Director; Dunlap; Greene; Houghton; Sloan; Ten Broeck
- Personnel - Lists (A-P) (Box 119, Folder 861)
- Personnel - Lists (R-Z) (Box 119, Folder 862)
- Personnel - Lists, 1921-1924, 1929-1935, 1939-1940, 1949-1950 (Box 119, Folder 863)
- Personnel - Lists - Miscellaneous, 1919-1949 (Box 119, Folder 864)
- Personnel - Resignations (A-S), 1922-1949 (Box 119, Folder 865)
- Personnel - Resignations (T-Z), 1922-1935 (Box 119, Folder 866)
- Pete-Pett (Box 120, Folder 867)
  Peter, W. W., 1921, 1946; Peterson, E. A. F., 1930; Pettus, William B., 1946, 1959; Pettus, W. Winston, 1937
- Pharmacology, 1920-1927, 1930-1941 (Box 120, Folder 868)
  Anderson; Brown, E. D.; Brown, G. L.; Candidates; Chen, Graham; Director; Fonahn, A.; Greene; Houghton; Pearce; Read, B. E.; Van Dyke
- Pharmacology - Ephedrine (Box 120, Folder 869)
  Bryne, J. D., 1926; Chen, K. K., 1926-1928; Cole, Rufus, 1926; Cowdry, E. V., 1926; Fisk, Frank B., 1927; Greene, 1928; Houghton, 1925-1927; Nadler, J. Ernest, 1926-1927; Read, Bernard E., 1927; Rodman, Robert W., 1932; Schloss, Oscar M., 1927; Schmidt, Carl F., 1925-1927; Schneller, E. J., 1927; Smith, Winford, 1926
- Pharmacology - Staff - Anderson, Frederick, 1933-1934 (Box 120, Folder 870)
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Frederick Anderson.
- Pharmacology - Staff - Anderson, Hamilton H., 1939-1964 (Box 120, Folder 870A)
  Items of special note in this folder include a pamphlet on travel to and from China (December 15, 1929), attached to a document dated February 1, 1940.
- Pharmacology - Staff - Chang, Chin, 1934 (Box 120, Folder 871)
- Pharmacology - Staff - Chen, (Mien) Graham, 1930-1933, 1936-1940, 1944, 1947 (Box 120, Folder 872)
- Pharmacology - Staff - Chen, Ko-kuei, 1922-1931, 1935, 1938 (Box 120, Folder 873)
- Pharmacology - Staff (Cho-Pa) (Box 120, Folder 874)
  Chou, Chin-huang, 1935-1936, 1945-1949; Chou, Tsan-quo; Dieuaide, Francis R., 1932; Feng, Chih-tung, 1922-1928; Hou, Hsiang-chuan, 1930-1933 (see also Physiology); How, (Kyan-ching) George, 1929; Hunt, Reid, 1920-1924; Kraemers, Edward (Materia Medica), 1919-1921; Liu, Ju-chiang, 1921-1930; Mills, Ralph G. (Materia Medica), 1918-1920; Pak, Chub-yung, 1926-1927, 1932; Pan, S. Y., 1963
- Pharmacology - Staff (Re-Sa) (Box 121, Folder 875)
  Read, Bernard E., 1920, 1923-1949, 1958, 1964 (see also Physiological Chemistry); Read, Katherine (Mrs. Bernard Read), 1971; Sah, (Pen-tieh) Peter, 1927-1934, 1940, 1945-1946
- Pharmacology - Staff (Sc-Wa) (Box 121, Folder 876)
  Schmidt, Carl F., 1920-1925, 1931-1932; Tsang, Kyang-pau, 1931; Van Dyke, Harry B., 1925, 1931-1938, 1942-1944, 1971; Wang, Chi-tao, 1949
- Pharmacy (Box 121, Folder 877)
  General, 1925-1926, 1932, 1941 (Amoss; Director); Scholarships (General, 1915-1917; Cheng, [Tsung-yi] Charles, 1915, 1918; Hsi, [Yin-dah] Abraham and David, 1915-1925)
- Pharmacy - Staff (Britland - Li, C. H.) (Box 121, Folder 878)
  Britland, Arthur J. D., 1916-1921; Cameron, John, 1920-1926, 1930, 1935, 1940-1949, 1956, 1962-1964; Chen, Lau-ying, 1948; Chu, Hung-pih, 1922, 1926-1929; Li, Ching-hua, 1948-1950
- Pharmacy - Staff (Li, R. - Tye) (Box 121, Folder 879)
  Li, (Chu) Richard, 1938-1940, 1946; Meng, Moody, 1921-1926, 1932; Moss, Gwen, 1930; Tu, Wang-heng, 1928-1937; Tye, Arthur, 1933-1941, 1945-1953
- Pha-Phy (Box 121, Folder 880)
  Pharmacy Act, 1922-1923 (Boulware, A. L.; Houghton; Johnson, Nelson T.) Philanthropy Fund, 1921-1922 Photographs, 1917-1935, 1940, 1966-1968 (see Box 165, see also Appendix C) (Charles Scribner's Sons; Cochrane; Director; Downing; Ferguson; Goodrich; Greene; McGraw-Hill Book Co., Inc.; Neergaard; Neurology - Woods; Peabody; Resident Director; Rolfe; Stragnell; Tichinin) Photographs - List of where used (see Box 165) Photographs - Lantern Slides (see Box 165, see also Appendix C) Physical Education, 1919-1921, 1925, 1933-1934, 1939 (Director; Greene; Houghton; Pearce, R. M.; Tsu, Caroline) Physical Examinations, 1919-1935 (Blood Pressure - Hall, G. A. M.; Chickering, Henry T.; Comptroller; Goodrich, L. C.; Greene; Houghton; Lee, Roger I.; Legge, Robert T.; Pearce, R. M.) Physical Plant, 1947 (Director)
  Items of special note in this folder include a cartoon of staff rounds at Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) with identification list, attached to a letter from Ferguson to Pearce (May 9, 1940).
- Physics (Box 121, Folder 881)
  General, 1921-1925 (Greene; Houghton; Vincent) Staff (Exner, Frank M., 1921-1925; Kwei, Chi-ting, 1920-1922; Stephenson, Bird R., 1919-1925; Stifler, William W., 1916-1925 (see also Pre-Medical School); Tong, Yung-tso, 1917; Yang, David K., 1922-1924, 1928)
  See also Box 162, Folder 18
- Physiological Chemistry, 1919-1924 (Box 121, Folder 882)
  Houghton; Pearce, R. M.; Read, Bernard E.
- Physiological Chemistry - Staff (E-M) (Box 122, Folder 883)
  Embrey, Hartley, 1919-1924, 1929, 1932; Lin, Kuo-hao, 1922-1924; Macallum, A. B., 1919-1924, 1934
- Physiological Chemistry - Staff (Re-Wo) (Box 122, Folder 884)
  Read, Bernard E., 1914-1924; Wong, San-yin, 1918-1923
- Physiological Chemistry - Staff (Wu-Ye (Box 122, Folder 885)
  Wu, Hsien, 1919-1924; Yen, (Tsai-yun) Daisy, 1923-1924
- Physiology, 1919-1934, 1941 (Box 122, Folder 886)
  Baldwin; Cathcart; Cruickshank; Director; Erlanger, Joseph; Fang T. P.; Greene; Houghton; Lim, Robert K. S.; Pearce; Resident Director; Smyly; Vincent
- Physiology - Staff (Bi-Ch) (Box 122, Folder 887)